Guide to the Jack L. Demmons Collection of Photographs of Bonner, Montana Circa 1890s-1960s
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana--Missoula
- Earl and Ada Fuller's cabin, 1970; Photo caption reads: The Earl and Ada Fuller cabin at Marshall Lake in the Blackfoot. (Lake in foreground; cabin, boat house, pine trees visible in photo; tear mark at right angle across and down middle of picture). Image from Photoboard #147 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 147_e_d)
- Sime Petaja and Francis, undated; Photo caption reads: Sime Petaja and Francis. (A toddler standing in front of her mother who is kneeling in an open field in the country; a small leafless tree or shrub is visible behind the people and the mountainside is visible in the background). Image from Photoboard #148 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 148_a_d)
- Girls group photo, undated; Photo caption reads: Front row - 1. Edith Ranstrom, 2. Darlene Miller, 3. Nina Petroff. 2d row - 1. Donna Karkanen, 2. Winnifred Thibodeau, 3. __, 4. Beverly Pine. Back row - 1. Ina Ranstrom, 2. Joyce Harris, 3. Mary Walker. Margaret 8. Margaret Akerson. (A group of young girls standing in the mill yard; canyon in background). Image from Photoboard #148 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 148_b_d)
- Ms. Nelson, undated; Photo caption reads: __ Nelson? Moved to Deer Lodge. (Photo of a woman in a long riding skirt and wide brimmed hat; standing by the railroad tracks near the Blackfoot and Clark Fork Rivers). Image from Photoboard #148 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 148_c_d)
- Group photo, undated; Photo caption reads: Front row: 1.__ 2. Earl Fuller. (Group of men gathered for picture in large room; front row is sitting on folding chairs others are standing). Image from Photoboard #148 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 148_d_d)
- Edith and Alma Laforge Rooney, undated; Photo caption reads: Left to Right - Edith Rooney, Alma Laforge Rooney. (Two women wearing long skirts standing next to railroad tracks; buildings and mountains visible in background). Image from Photoboard #148 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 148_e_d)
- Class photo, undated; Photo caption reads: 1st row - 1. Burt Rumsey. 7. Renoldo LaForge. 8. Leo Mosrell?. 9. Clarence Haaglund. 10. Leonard Nelson. 11. Joe Boileau. 12. Bernard Sorenson. 2nd row - 6. Ida Mattson. 7. Aafje deWit. 8. Margaret ( ) Akerson. 9. __ Thomas. 10. __ Halvary. 3rd row - 1. Gene Gednrow. 8. __ Weimer? 4th row - 1. Corine Daigle. (Class photo; group of children and teachers; some are sitting and others are standing). Image from Photoboard #148 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 148_f_d)
- Simi and Francis Petaja, undated; Photo caption reads: Simi Petaja and son Francis.(Child is standing in front of mother in an open field; small bush partly visible to their right; train; West Riverside; Mountain in background). Image from Photoboard #148 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 148_g_d)
- Group photo, undated; Photo caption reads: Left to Right, Front row - 1.____ 2. John McKay? 3. Monk Doucette. 4. Carrie Pleasant. 2nd row - 1.____ 2. Billie Doucette. 3. Ethel Farmer. 4. Donna LaForge. 5. Margaret LaForge. 6. Ada Fuller. 7. Rosie Wagner. 8. Fred Farmer. Back row - 1. Albert Wagner. 2. Mary LaForge. 3. Luella McKay. (Group of people of multiple generations; trees visible in background). Image from Photoboard #148 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 148_h_d)
- Bill Lien at Placid Lake, undated; Photo caption reads: Bill Lien at Placid Lake. (Man standing with hands on hips in an open field; trees and part of a car visible in background). Image from Photoboard #148 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 148_i_d)
- Friends and fishing, undated; Photo caption reads: Arnie Ranta, Ernest Ranta, Eugene Lavoie, David Halme, Ivan Levesque. (Group of men stand together holding large fish between them). Image from Photoboard #149 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 149_a_d)
- Streetcar station, undated; Photo caption reads: Mabel Cyr, Lottie Michaud, Sophie LaCasse, Leona Levesque, Della Godbout, Rene Levesque, Patrick Cyr. (Group of people at streetcar station; young children and women are sitting and men are standing). Image from Photoboard #149 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 149_b_d)
- Mrs. Piltz, undated; Photo caption reads: Mrs. Piltz. (Woman sitting in chair outside on lawn doing needlepoint; side of house visible in background). Image from Photoboard #149 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 149_c_d)
- Streetcar, undated; Photo caption reads: Streetcar. (Streetcar on tracks near Milltown; large "B" on front of car; homes and mountain visible in background). Image from Photoboard #149 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 149_d_d)
- The old Carl Jacobson home, undated; Photo caption reads: The old Carl Jacobson home. (Two young children playing in yard; carriage on porch; bench style chair in front of building; patches of snow on the ground). Image from Photoboard #149 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 149_e_d)
- Billy and Rose Thibodeau, undated; Photo caption reads: Wm. (Billy) and Rose Thibodeau. (Studio portrait of man and woman). Image from Photoboard #149 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 149_f_d)
- Hamma family, undated; Photo caption reads: Hamma family. Ina, Martha, Mary, Helen Nousianen, Onnie, and Charlie. (Children standing in yard in front of buildings; they are in descending order tallest to shortest, from left to right). Image from Photoboard #149 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 149_g_d)
- Levesque family portrait, undated; Photo caption reads: Levesque family Left to right: Ivan, Ilene, Leona Cyr, Rene, Anne, Eldon, Junior Rene. (Family portrait; front row is sitting; back row is standing). Image from Photoboard #149 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 149_h_d)
- Ed Violette, undated; Photo caption reads: Ed Violette. (Ed and an unidentified man in a studio portrait). Image from Photoboard #149 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 149_i_d)
- Ingeborg Michelson, undated; Photo caption reads: Ingeborg Michelson. (In dress with hat; standing between two sets of tracks). Image from Photoboard #150 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 150_a_d)
- Ruins left after 1919 fire at ACM Mill, undated; Photo caption reads: ACM Mill, burned in 1919. In background, #1, cook house, #2 bunk house. (Burned wreckage of cook house and bunk house; teepee burner in background). Image from Photoboard #150 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 150_b_d)
- Gordon Trenary, undated; Photo caption reads: Gordon Trenary. (Standing in front of picket fence by street). Image from Photoboard #150 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 150_c_d)
- ACM Mill after 1919 fire, undated; No photo caption. (ACM Mill after 1919 fire; 1 cookhouse, 2 bunkhouse; foreground burned ruins; "58" handwritten in upper right hand corner of photo). Image from Photoboard #150 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 150_d_d)
- Bill Doucette and Clifford LaForge, undated; Photo caption reads: Bill Doucette; Clifford LaForge. (Bill is wearing a formal service uniform; Clifford, wearing suspenders, stands beside Bill; outdoors; standing on wood sidewalk; house in background). Image from Photoboard #150 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 150_f_d)
- ACM Mill in the early days, undated; Photo caption reads: Early day view of ACM mill. (Taken from hillside; "69" handwritten at top right hand corner of photo). Image from Photoboard #150 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 150_g_d)
- The Rooney family, undated; Photo caption reads: Marjorie Rooney, Mrs. Fannie Rooney, Mr. Arthur Rooney, Edith Rooney. ("Fannie" and "Arthur" are handwritten on the photo caption). Image from Photoboard #150 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 150_h_d)
- Pele Demmons, undated; Photo caption reads: Pele Demmons. (A member of the first Bonner school board). (Studio photo; 1880s or 1890s; creases on photo). Image from Photoboard #151 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 151_a_d)
- Leo Dufresne gets a bath, undated; Photo caption reads: Leo Dufresne. (Baby in washtub; outdoors; house in background). Image from Photoboard #151 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 151_b_d)
- Seberena and Al McDaniels, undated; Photo caption reads: Seberena and Al McDaniels. (Standing on wood sidewalk in Bonner). Image from Photoboard #151 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 151_c_d)
- Missoula in the 1930s, circa 1930s; Photo caption reads: Old time Missoula, 1930s. (Looking north across Orange Street bridge; street lamps; courthouse; Mt. Jumbo and Rattlesnake drainage in the distance; automobiles crossing bridge). Image from Photoboard #151 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 151_d_d)
- Eldon Levesque and Cecil Bond, 1944; Photo caption reads: Eldon Levesque, Cecil Bond. April 25, 1944. (Eldon wears a sailor's uniform; Cecil wears Army slacks, shirt and hat). Image from Photoboard #151 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 151_e_d)
- Bonner eighth grade class of 1937-1938, Photo caption reads: Bonner 8th Grade Class. May 27, 1938. Left to right - front to back: Bob Mast, Mary Opal Johnson. Leo Dufresne, Leo Fleming, Bill Bush, Buzzy Bateman, Clifton Moss, Ernest Hunt, Miss Erkkila. Albertine Kyle, Francis Robinson, Peggy Bidiscome, Bessie Sandburg, Virginia Niemi, Mary Barta, Jack Kern, Mr. Bill Akin. Renae Levesque, George Cyr, Jack Anderson, Carl Reinhardt, Frank Inman, Cecil Madsen, Roy Swartz, Carl Ranstrom. Mildred Cummings, Harriet Bush, Helen Baird, Audrie Hathaway. (Students sit in desks). Image from Photoboard #151 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 151_f_d)
- Dorothy Waddington, 1933; Photo caption reads: Dorothy Waddington, 8th grade 1933. (Standing in classroom; Christmas mural in background; map on chalkboard, above it written "Who can put a thumbtack on T145-R7W? on T33N-R57?"). Image from Photoboard #152 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 152_a_d)
- George Daigle, 1933; Photo caption reads: George Daigle, 8th grade, 1933. (Stands in front of school steps; snow on shoes, hands on hips). Image from Photoboard #152 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 152_b_d)
- Undated Bonner School grades 1 through 4 students and teachers, Photo caption reads: Bonner School 1-4 grades. (Unknown school photograph; at least 70 children stand on school steps and in front of school; three women teachers on back row on steps; two men or older boys stand in back row of ground-level; image file name changed, original file name was 152_c_d_acc). Image from Photoboard #152 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 168_f_d2)
- Alice Violette gets pushed on a swing by Guy Olson, undated; Photo caption reads: Guy Olson, Alice Violette. (Alice, wearing dress, on swing; Guy pushing swing; teeter totters behind swings; possibly outhouse in background; possibly mountain above Piltzville in far background). Image from Photoboard #152 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 152_d_d)
- Gerda Carlson, undated; Photo caption reads: Gerda Carlson. (Young girl outdoors; old Bonner School and mouth of Blackfoot Canyon in far background). Image from Photoboard #152 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 152_e_d)
- Bonner School teachers, undated; Photo caption reads: Bonner School teachers. Bottom: Alta Ledgerwood. Left to right: Lucille Speer, Muriel Rossiter, Eunice Brown, Ella Falligan, Letty Nelson, Lilah Eberle, St. Germaine, Susie Fisher. (Undated photograph; standing in front of school). Image from Photoboard #152 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 152_f_d)
- Undated class photograph, Photo caption reads: Row 1: 1.___ 2.____ 3.____ 4. Gunhild Werner 5. Mabel Cyr 6. Alice Lien. 7. Row 2: 1, Oscar Werner; 2. Ted Olson; 3____. 4. Eino Karkanen 5. Denny Morreau; 6____. 7. Alma Rooney 8.____ 9. Eva Hamma. Row 3: 1.____ 2. Mary Newport (teacher). 3.____ 4. (Undated class photo; students and teachers on school steps). Image from Photoboard #152 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 152_g_d)
- Undated school photograph, Photo caption reads: Row 1: 1.____ 2.____ 3. Grace LeClair 4. Freda Nearman 5. Edna Teague 6.____ 7____. 8.____ 9.____ 10.____ 11. Hazel Anderson 12. Corrine Smith 13. Irene Dodson 14. Hazel Fowler 15. Dorothy Gosden. Row 2: 1. Alice Lien 2. Florence Fowler 3. Alice LaForge 4. Alice Violette 5. Laura Nelson 6. Row 3: 1. Annie Karkanen 2. Margaret Smith 3. Freda Salmonson 4. Martha Larson 5. Julia Moss 6. Row 4: 1. Dolly Smith 2. Ada Thibodeau 3. Hazel Beadle 4. Lilah Lundy 5. Freda Johnson 6. Edna Labbe 7. Row 5: 1.____ 2. Bernice Dodson 4. George Cyr 5. Eddie Ouilette 6. Ed Labbe 9. Row 6: 1.____ 2.____ 3.____ 4. Wes Fowler 5. Miss St. Germaine 6. Vern Hill 7. ____ Row 7: 1.____ 2. ____ 3.____ 4. Jennie McGregor; 5. (Undated school photograph; boys in back row hold basketball over Miss St. Germaine's head; students cut out of photo at edges of front rows). Image from Photoboard #152 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 152_h_d)
- School children, undated; Photo caption reads: Gaylord Gervois Bill Pleasant, Robert McKay, Nona Taylor, Bertha Hill, Fay Chaffey, Lillian Akin, Carl Brandt, Neil Hekkila, Peggy Ross.(Undated photograph; school children, some with books, pose in front of school; not all students identified). Image from Photoboard #152 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 152_i_d)
- Bonner School in 1957, Photo caption reads: Picture of the Bonner School after the first addition of the new plant was finished, 1957. Image from Photoboard #153 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 153_a_d)
- Lee Thibodeau and Orvil Kinonen, undated; Photo caption reads: Left to right - Lee Thibodeau and Orvil Kinonen, World War II. (In Army uniforms; standing on steps of train). Image from Photoboard #153 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 153_b_d)
- Mildred Cummings Larson, Ruth Cummings Therriault, and Ruby Cummings Martell, 1957; Photo caption reads: Left to right - Mildred Cummings Larson, Ruth Cummings Therriault, Ruby Cummings Martell. ("Ruby" crossed out and "Mildred" written beside name; Milred Cummings Martell ("Mildred" crossed out and "Ruby" written to side). Image from Photoboard #153 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 153_c_d)
- Eddie Therriault, 1936; Photo caption reads: Eddie Therriault, 1936.(Stands on sidewalk by vine; stands with his left hand in pocket; hat; side of house). Image from Photoboard #153 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 153_d_d)
- The Hintz family celebrate a 50th wedding anniversary, undated; Photo caption reads: 50th wedding anniversary. Left to right: Hintz family. Bernice, Clifford, Norma, Beatrice, Gus, Ethel, Elva, Ray. (Gus and Elva appear to be the anniversary couple; faded photo). Image from Photoboard #153 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 153_e_d)
- Tibby and Emily Thibodeau, undated; Photo caption reads: Tibby and Emily Thibodeau. (Emily on left; in front of Bonner garage; Tibby’s arm around Emily’s shoulder). Image from Photoboard #153 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 153_f_d)
- Newly installed Bonner Mill debarker, undated; Photo caption reads: Picture of the Bonner Mill debarker when it was first installed. Image from Photoboard #153 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 153_g_d)
- Eddie and Ruth Therriault, undated; Photo caption reads: Eddie and Ruth Therriault. (Indoors; wearing coats). Image from Photoboard #153 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 153_h_d)
- Ray, Francis, Jim and Bob Hintz, undated; Photo caption reads: Left to right - Ray, Francis, Jim, and Bob Hintz. (Studio photograph). Image from Photoboard #153 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 153_i_d)
- Mrs. Alex Lanoue in 1905, Photo caption reads: Hank Cadieux's grandmother, Mrs. Alex Lanoue. She originally came to the United States from Canada and first settled in the Huson-6 Mile area. Picture was taken in 1905. Image from Photoboard #154 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 154_a_d)
- Vic Kinonen, undated; Photo caption reads: Vic Kinonen. Image from Photoboard #154 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 154_b_d)
- Ernest Lizotte, 1905; Photo caption reads: Ernest Lizotte. (Wearing civilian clothes and a top hat; with pipe; in Bonner; house and leafless trees in background). Image from Photoboard #154 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 154_c_d)
- Jack Teague during World War II, undated; Photo caption reads: Jack Teague, U.S. Navy, World War II. (Buoy hanging in background says "NTS Farragut Ida). Image from Photoboard #154 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 154_d_d)
- Portrait of Klass DeWit, 1927; Photo caption reads: Klass DeWit, 1927. (Studio photograph). Image from Photoboard #154 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 154_e_d)
- Arne Ranta, undated; Photo caption reads: Arne Ranta, U.S. Army, World War II. (Leans on jeep; barracks in background). Image from Photoboard #154 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 154_f_d)
- Ellen Kinonen, 1942; Photo caption reads: Ellen Kinonen during World War II days.(Wearing t-shirt that says "U.S. Army Ft. Lewis"). Image from Photoboard #154 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 154_g_d)
- Portrait of Aafje DeWit Demmons, 1929; Photo caption reads: Aafje DeWit Demmons, 1929. Image from Photoboard #154 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 154_h_d)
- Ernest Lizotte with unidentified soldier, 1942; Photo caption reads: Ernest Lizotte, U.S. Army Air Corps, World War II. Taken at Camp Sutton, North Carolina in June, 1942. (Tents in background). Image from Photoboard #154 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 154_i_d)
- The Wisherds, circa 1921; Photo caption reads: About 1921. Grace and Art Wisherd, Mrs. Wisherd. (Three adults; big dog in front of Art; house and mountain in background). Image from Photoboard #155 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 155_a_d)
- School house where Grace Wisherd taught, 1920; Photo caption reads: The school house where Grace Wisherd taught In Montana 1920. (Pine trees; stumps; American flag flies over school). Image from Photoboard #155 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 155_b_d)
- Ray Johns and others, undated; Photo caption reads: Ray Johns. (Twelve individuals; adults and children; in front of canvas-topped jalopy). Image from Photoboard #155 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 155_c_d)
- Mr. and Mrs. Harry Peterson on their wedding day, undated; Photo caption reads: Mr. and Mrs. Charles Niemi, Mr. and Mrs. Harry Peterson, Mr. and Mrs. Hans Peterson. (Wedding photograph of the Harry Petersons; women wearing big corsages; St. Ann’s Catholic Church; Bonner Mountain in background). Image from Photoboard #155 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 155_d_d)
- Two Piltzville homes in 1930, Photo caption reads: 1930 Anna and Peter Peterson house at right (presently Aafje Demmons). Alfred Peterson at left. (Two homes, one story on left, two story on right, at base of mountain in Piltzville). Image from Photoboard #155 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 155_e_d)
- Boys pose in front of Sleeping Child cabin, undated; No caption. (Sixteen boys in two rows in front of cabin; man with folded arms to right of boys, all boys wearing hats; scribbled in cursive under photo “Sleeping Child cabin ... Melvin Akin .. 7th Jack Lubrecht ..Soup Johnson .. Wagner .. Sam Olson). Image from Photoboard #155 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 155_f_d)
- The Hans Peterson house in Piltzville, undated; Photo caption reads: Hans Peterson house in Piltzville. (Two men in black suits and hats sit on the front porch with hands to chins; young girl in white dress stands on porch; young boy in black with no hat in front yard; snow on ground). Image from Photoboard #155 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 155_g_d)
- Hans Peterson with Mabel Johnson and Gloria, undated; Photo caption reads: Hans Peterson, Mabel Johnson and Gloria. (Three adults sit on couch; baby on lap of woman on right). Image from Photoboard #155 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 155_h_d)
- Mabel Johnson, undated; Photo caption reads: Mabel Johnson. (Wearing hat and fur stole; sits on porch step with black and white dog). Image from Photoboard #155 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 155_i_d)
- Paul and Kenny Lizotte, undated; Photo caption reads: Paul and Kenny Lizotte. (Two men lean on car; Paul in Army uniform; on street of Milltown?; dog on ground in front of men). Image from Photoboard #157 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 157_a_d)
- Walter Hook and Orv Kinonen relax by Black Bridge, undated; Photo caption reads: Walter Hook in foreground and Orv (Honey) Kinonen. (Two teenage boys; Hook stands laughing on river bank holding something; Orv lies on back on plank diving board in swim trunks; another boy in water holding onto diving board; just to south of east end of Black Bridge). Image from Photoboard #157 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 157_b_d)
- Barney Hegdal, undated; Photo caption reads: Barney Hegdal. (Man sits on flight of steps). Image from Photoboard #157 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 157_c_d)
- Bert Kyle, undated; Photo caption reads: Bert Kyle. (Older man sits, head resting on hand; poster on wall says "Champion!... Mountain" man on horseback with dog in foreground on poster). Image from Photoboard #157 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 157_d_d)
- Stanley Wold, undated; Photo caption reads: Stanley Wold. (Stands in house holding a small fish). Image from Photoboard #157 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 157_e_d)
- Orv and Ellen Kinonen, undated; Photo caption reads: Orv (Honey) and Ellen Kinonen, World War II. (Hugging; Orv in Army uniform; by car in front of house). Image from Photoboard #157 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 157_f_d)
- Ella Falligan, undated; Photo caption reads: Ella Falligan. Picture was taken prior to 1905. (Studio photograph of girl of about 12 or 13 wearing white dress and hat). Image from Photoboard #157 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 157_g_d)
- Ola Pearson, undated; Photo caption reads: Ola Pearson. (Profile of older man wearing hat and plaid jacket; arm resting on rail). Image from Photoboard #157 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 157_h_d)
- Hank Cadieux's uncle with an unidentified woman, 1907; Photo caption reads: Hank Cadieux's uncle - Ontario Canada, 1907. (Studio portrait of a man standing by an unidentified woman sitting in a chair). Image from Photoboard #156 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 156_a_d)
- Carl and Bob Rooney, undated; Photo caption reads: Left to right - Carl Rooney, Bob Rooney. (Two men stand in clearing in forest). Image from Photoboard #156 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 156_b_d)
- Louis Cadieux, 1896; Photo caption reads: Louis Cadieux - Hank Cadieux's dad, taken in 1896. At this time he worked for the N.P.R.R. (Studio portrait of man standing.) (Duplicate of Photo 157_i_d_acc.). Image from Photoboard #156 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 156_c_d)
- Five unidentified women and a young boy sit by a fire pit, undated; Photo caption reads: Unidentified, (youngster on board). (Five elderly women sit around a picnic pit; young boy on board bench on right side of photo). Image from Photoboard #158 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 158_a_d)
- Hazel Splann with Frank and Mildred Dufresne, undated; Photo caption reads: Hazel Splann, Frank Dufresne, Mildred Dufresne. (Three adults sit in teacher's lounge, Bonner School; snow, hedge, mill visible through window). Image from Photoboard #158 (Digital image Digital Image, Photo number 158_b_d)